steinhafels.com 2017-09-21

# Steinhafels - Privacy Policy

At Steinhafels Furniture, we respect and share your concerns regarding privacy. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) discloses what information is gathered about steinhafels.com website users and visitors (the “Site”) and how that information is used. The Site is owned or operated by Steinhafels Furniture (the “Company,” “we” or “us”), and we use the personal information we receive from Steinhafels.com as described below. By using the Site, or sharing your information with us, you consent to and accept the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

We keep information entered during ordering and registering confidential. 

You may also create an account through steinhafels.com at any time by providing your email address and designating a unique access password. You do not need to create an account in order to visit our Site. For your privacy and security, we do not store credit card numbers in your account. 

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. In some instances, we partner with other companies to provide our products and services to you. Some of these companies are given access to some, or all, of the information you provide to us and may use cookies ( _see definition below_ ) on our behalf. These companies are restricted from using your information in any way other than providing products and services through our web site. 

As a customer or subscriber, you may occasionally receive e-mail communications about new Steinhafel products or special offers we think you’ll like and requests for feedback. You may opt-out of receiving future communications from us any time we request your personal information by email, by clicking on the link at the bottom of emails you receive from us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process such requests in a timely manner. 

Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your hard drive to remember aspects of your visits to a particular web site. We may use cookies to help us improve your shopping experience by tracking which areas of our site are most and least popular. We never use cookies to store confidential information like passwords or credit card information. We may also collect certain technical information from your computer. This technical information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer’s operating system, browser type and the address of a referring website, if any. We will use such information only to investigate and identify unauthorized activities. 

Additionally, we use Hotjar ([www.hotjar.com](https://www.hotjar.com/)) in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize our website. Hotjar is a service that analyzes how users use our website (e.g. how much time they spend on which parts of the website, which links they choose to click, etc.) and this provides us with feedback on how best to design our website. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on this [link](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy). You can also opt-out of Hotjar’s collecting and storing of data about your usage by following this [link](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out). 

Unless otherwise indicated herein, our website and service are governed and operated in accordance with the laws of the United States. 

Steinhafels stores personal information in the United States. To facilitate our operations, we may transfer and access such information from around the world, including from other countries in which we have users. 

YOU CONSENT TO THE TRANSFER OF DATA, INCLUDING THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE AND SUBMIT VIA THE SERVICE, TO THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA. YOU ARE INFORMED THAT THE UNITED STATES IS NOT PRESENTLY DETERMINED TO HAVE AN ADEQUATE LEVEL OF PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION AS ARTICULATED IN THE EUROPEAN UNION’S DATA PROTECTION DIRECTIVE 95/46/EC AND HAS NOT RECEIVED A SIMILAR DESIGNATION OF ADEQUACY BY ANY OTHER FOREIGN DATA PROTECTION AUTHORITY. YOU AGREE TO THE TRANSFER OF YOUR DATA AND PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES, HOWEVER, TO BE USED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

This Site and service are not targeted towards, nor intended for use by, persons under the age of 13. If you are not at least 13 years of age, do not access, use, or register on the website. We do not want to or knowingly collect personal information from persons under age 13 (in which case we will terminate and delete your account and all information contained therein) without prior parental consent. Unless we have knowledge to the contrary, we will presume that all personally identifiable information collected by the website or service is from persons age 13 and over. By using the website or service, you represent and warrant that you are 13 years of age or older. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process personal data, please contact us at itdept@steinhafels.com.

This Privacy Policy was posted on March 31, 2017. We may occasionally modify this Privacy Policy.
